<!--DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE - It is generated and any changes made will be overwritten--><div xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
     xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
     xmlns:f="http://hl7.org/fhir"
     class="markdown-toc">
   <p>Contents:</p>
   <ul>
      <li>
         <a href="#1">Behavior: Capability Statements</a>
      </li>
      <li>
         <a href="#2">Structures: Resource Profiles</a>
      </li>
      <li>
         <a href="#3">Structures: Extension Definitions</a>
      </li>
      <li>
         <a href="#4">Terminology: Value Sets</a>
      </li>
      <li>
         <a href="#5">Terminology: Code Systems</a>
      </li>
      <li>
         <a href="#6">Example: Example Instances</a>
      </li>
   </ul>
</div>
<div xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
     xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
     xmlns:f="http://hl7.org/fhir">
   <p>This page provides a list of the FHIR artifacts defined as part of this implementation guide.</p>
   <a name="1"> </a>
   <h3>Behavior: Capability Statements </h3>
   <p>The following artifacts define the specific capabilities that different types of systems are expected to have in order to comply with this implementation guide.  Systems complying with the implementation guide are expected to declare conformance to one or more of the following capability statements.</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-producer-server.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/producer-server">Producer Server CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Producer Server when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide. Producers include systems that are primary producers of patient healthcare information.  This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that a Da Vinci DEQM Producer Server could support. Servers have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-consumer-server.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/consumer-server">Consumer Server CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Consumer Server when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide.  Consumers include systems that are primary consumers of patient healthcare information and systems that consume data from Producers.  This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that a Da Vinci DEQM Consumer Server could support. Servers have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-receiver-server.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/receiver-server">Receiver Server CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Receiver Server when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide. Receivers include systems that are primary receivers of Measure data such as payers as well as public health and other healthcare-related agencies.  This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that a Da Vinci DEQM Receiver Server could support. Servers have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-reporter-client.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/reporter-client">Reporter Client CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Reporter Client when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide.  Reporters include systems that are primary reporters of patient healthcare information and systems that consume data from Producers.   This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that a Da Vinci DEQM Reporter Client could support. Clients have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-producer-client.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/producer-client">Producer Client CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Producer Client when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide. Producers include systems that are primary producers of patient healthcare information.  This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that are  Da Vinci DEQM Producer Client could support. Clients have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CapabilityStatement-consumer-client.html"
                     title="CapabilityStatement/consumer-client">Consumer Client CapabilityStatement</a>
               </td>
               <td>This profile defines the expected capabilities of a Da Vinci DEQM Consumer Client when conforming to the Da Vinci DEQM Implementation Guide.  Consumers include systems that are primary consumers of patient healthcare information and systems that consume data from Producers.   This CapabilityStatement resource includes the complete list of the *recommended*  Da Vinci DEQM profiles and RESTful operations that a Da Vinci DEQM Consumer Client could support. Clients have the option of choosing from this list based on their local use cases and other contextual requirements.</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
   <a name="2"> </a>
   <h3>Structures: Resource Profiles </h3>
   <p>These define constraints on FHIR resources that need to be complied with by conformant implementations</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-medicationrequest-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/medicationrequest-deqm">DEQM MedicationRequest Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>The DEQM MedicationRequest Profile describes a medication prescription</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-practitioner-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/practitioner-deqm">DEQM Practitioner Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>The DEQM Practitioner Profile defines the constraints for representing the practitioner who performed the measure or to which is attesting.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-summary-measurereport-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/summary-measurereport-deqm">DEQM Summary MeasureReport Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>[MeasureReport] is used as an organizer for both data exchange for measure and for measure reporting.  Three profiles on the MeasureReport resource are defined in this guide to delineate these different uses.  The **DEQM Summary MeasureReport Profile** defined here is used when a measure is reported to an aggregator for a group of patients. It contains all of the data that is relevant to generate the report including the measure outcome and is similar to a QRDA Category 3 report.  Unlike the [DEQM Individual MeasureReport Profile], the report is typically transacted as a single MeasureReport report.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-indv-measurereport-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/indv-measurereport-deqm">DEQM Individual MeasureReport Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>[MeasureReport] is used as an organizer for both data exchange for measure and for measure reporting.  Three profiles on the MeasureReport resource are defined in this guide to delineate these different uses.     The **DEQM Individual MeasureReport Profile** defined here is used when a measure is reported to an aggregator for one specific patient. It contains all of the data that is relevant to generate the report including the measure outcome and is similar to a QRDA Category 1 report.  In addition to the MeasureReport, the report would be collected in a Bundle with the Organization, Patient and any other resources that were used to calculate this measure.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-datax-measurereport-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/datax-measurereport-deqm">DEQM Data Exchange MeasureReport Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>[MeasureReport] is used as an organizer for both data exchange for measure and for measure reporting.  Three profiles on the MeasureReport resource are defined in this guide to delineate these different uses.
When a data producer needs to send data to a data consumer, they use the **DEQM Data-Exchange MeasureReport Profile** defined here.  The `type` element in this profile is set to “data-collection”.  Along with the MeasureReport profile, the data producer sends the Organization, Patient and any relevant resources for the measure they have produced data on.  When a data producer sends a MeasureReport and the associated data, they may not have all the data that is required to calculate the measure report.  Additional data may need to be collected later or there may be additional data used in the measure that the aggregator owns such as a continuous coverage period requirement.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-coverage-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/coverage-deqm">DEQM  Coverage Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>The DEQM Coverage Profile defines the constraints for representing  the subscriber information to the Payer.  This along with the patient first name, last name, date of birth and gender allows the payer to identify the member in their system.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-organization-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/organization-deqm">DEQM Organization Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>The DEQM Organization Profile defines the constraints for representing the organization for which the practitioner was working when he performed the measure to which he is attesting.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-medicationadministration-deqm.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/medicationadministration-deqm">DEQM MedicationAdministration Profile</a>
               </td>
               <td>The DEQM MedicationAdministration Profile describes the event of a patient consuming or otherwise being administered a medication</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
   <a name="3"> </a>
   <h3>Structures: Extension Definitions </h3>
   <p>These define constraints on FHIR data types that need to be complied with by conformant implementations</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-measureScoring.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-measureScoring">DEQM Measure Scoring Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>Indicates how the calculation is performed for the measure, including proportion, ratio, continuous-variable, and cohort. The value set is extensible, allowing additional measure scoring types to be represented. It is expected to be the same as the scoring element on the referenced Measure</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-alternateScoreType.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-alternateScoreType">DEQM Alternate Score Type Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>Possible value types for the measureScore elements *in addition to* the standard [Quantity](http://hl7.org/fhir/STU3/datatypes.html#quantity) type. The alternate type is determined by the Quality Measure [Aggregate Method](http://hl7.org/fhir/us/cqfmeasures/2019May/StructureDefinition-cqfm-aggregateMethod.html) extension used on the Measure.   The reported type of the measureScore for continuous variable measures is determined by the result type of the aggregate method operation.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-reporterGroup.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-reporterGroup">DEQM Reporter Group Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>Group of practitioners responsible for a report. This extension is used to provide the capability to allow the participating practitioners to be documented.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-reportingVendor.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-reportingVendor">DEQM Reporting Vendor Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>A reference to the vendor who queried the data, calculated results and/or generated the report. The 'reporting vendor' is intended to represent the submitting entity when it is not the same as the reporting entity.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-certificationIdentifier.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-certificationIdentifier">DEQM Certification Identifier Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>An identifier that represents the EHR certication number (CERHT).  See [Certified EHR Technology](https://www.cms.gov/regulations-and-guidance/legislation/ehrincentiveprograms/certification.html) For more information.</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="StructureDefinition-extension-submitDataUpdateType.html"
                     title="StructureDefinition/extension-submitDataUpdateType">DEQM Submit Data Update Type Extension</a>
               </td>
               <td>This Extension supports the concepts 'incremental' and 'snapshot'.

- The DEQM Consumer Server **SHALL** use this Extension to advertise whether it supports [snapshot](index.html#incremental-update) or [incremental](index.html#snapshot-update) updates for the [DEQM Submit Data transaction](datax.html#submit-data).
- The DEQM Producer Client **SHALL** use this Extension to indicate whether the payload is a snapshot or incremental update for DEQM Submit Data transaction.
 When responding to the [DEQM Collect Data transaction](datax.html#collect-data), the DEQM Producer Server **SHALL**  value it 'incremental' if the `lastReceivedOn` parameter is present or 'snapshot if the `lastReceivedOn` parameter is absent.</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
   <a name="4"> </a>
   <h3>Terminology: Value Sets </h3>
   <p>These define sets of codes used by systems conforming with this implementation guide</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="ValueSet-update-type.html" title="ValueSet/update-type">DEQM Update Type Value Set</a>
               </td>
               <td>Concepts for how a DEQM Consumer supports data exchange updates. The choices are snapshot or incremental updates</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
   <a name="5"> </a>
   <h3>Terminology: Code Systems </h3>
   <p>These define new code systems used by systems conforming with this implementation guide</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="CodeSystem-update-type.html" title="CodeSystem/update-type">DEQM Update Type Code System</a>
               </td>
               <td>Concepts for how a DEQM Consumer supports data exchange updates. The choices are snapshot or incremental updates</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
   <a name="6"> </a>
   <h3>Example: Example Instances </h3>
   <p>These are example instances that show what data produced and consumed by systems conforming with this implementation guide might look like</p>
   <p>
      <table class="grid">
         <col style="width:20%"/>
         <tbody>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Organization-organization02.html"
                     title="Organization/organization02">Organization02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Organization02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Patient-patient02.html" title="Patient/patient02">Patient02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Patient02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-summ-medicare-stratification-example.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/summ-medicare-stratification-example">Summ Medicare Stratification Example</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Summ Medicare Stratification Example example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Location-location03.html" title="Location/location03">Location03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Location03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-summ-measurereport01.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/summ-measurereport01">Summ Measurereport01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Summ Measurereport01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-datax-measurereport02.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/datax-measurereport02">Datax Measurereport02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Datax Measurereport02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Parameters-mrp-submit-task.html"
                     title="Parameters/mrp-submit-task">Mrp Submit Task</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Mrp Submit Task example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-multiple-indv-mrp-obs-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/multiple-indv-mrp-obs-report">Multiple Indv Mrp Obs Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Multiple Indv Mrp Obs Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Measure-measure-mrp-example.html"
                     title="Measure/measure-mrp-example">Measure Mrp Example</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Measure Mrp Example example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-datax-measurereport03.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/datax-measurereport03">Datax Measurereport03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Datax Measurereport03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Location-location02.html" title="Location/location02">Location02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Location02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-single-indv-vte-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/single-indv-vte-report">Single Indv Vte Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Single Indv Vte Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Parameters-col-submit-collect-obs.html"
                     title="Parameters/col-submit-collect-obs">Col Submit Collect Obs</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Col Submit Collect Obs example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Patient-patient03.html" title="Patient/patient03">Patient03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Patient03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Coverage-coverage01.html" title="Coverage/coverage01">Coverage01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Coverage01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Organization-organization03.html"
                     title="Organization/organization03">Organization03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Organization03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Library-library-mrp-example.html"
                     title="Library/library-mrp-example">Library Mrp Example</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Library Mrp Example example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Library-exm130-fhir-r4.html" title="Library/exm130-fhir-r4">Exm130 Fhir R4</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Exm130 Fhir R4 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Organization-organization04.html"
                     title="Organization/organization04">Organization04</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Organization04 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Parameters-mrp-submit-obs.html" title="Parameters/mrp-submit-obs">Mrp Submit Obs</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Mrp Submit Obs example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Observation-observation01.html" title="Observation/observation01">Observation01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Observation01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-multiple-summ-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/multiple-summ-report">Multiple Summ Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Multiple Summ Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Device-deqm-software-system-example.html"
                     title="Device/deqm-software-system-example">Deqm Software System Example</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Deqm Software System Example example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-indv-measurereport01.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/indv-measurereport01">Indv Measurereport01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Indv Measurereport01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-indv-measurereport02.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/indv-measurereport02">Indv Measurereport02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Indv Measurereport02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-multiple-indv-mrp-task-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/multiple-indv-mrp-task-report">Multiple Indv Mrp Task Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Multiple Indv Mrp Task Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Encounter-Encounter01.html" title="Encounter/Encounter01">Encounter01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Encounter01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Observation-observation03.html" title="Observation/observation03">Observation03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Observation03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-single-indv-mrp-task-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/single-indv-mrp-task-report">Single Indv Mrp Task Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Single Indv Mrp Task Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-single-indv-col-obs-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/single-indv-col-obs-report">Single Indv Col Obs Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Single Indv Col Obs Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Practitioner-practitioner01.html"
                     title="Practitioner/practitioner01">Practitioner01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Practitioner01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-indv-measurereport03.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/indv-measurereport03">Indv Measurereport03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Indv Measurereport03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Coverage-coverage02.html" title="Coverage/coverage02">Coverage02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Coverage02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Location-location01.html" title="Location/location01">Location01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Location01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Bundle-single-indv-mrp-obs-report.html"
                     title="Bundle/single-indv-mrp-obs-report">Single Indv Mrp Obs Report</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Single Indv Mrp Obs Report example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-summ-measurereport02.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/summ-measurereport02">Summ Measurereport02</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Summ Measurereport02 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="MeasureReport-datax-measurereport01.html"
                     title="MeasureReport/datax-measurereport01">Datax Measurereport01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Datax Measurereport01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Task-Task01.html" title="Task/Task01">Task01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Task01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Organization-organization01.html"
                     title="Organization/organization01">Organization01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Organization01 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Coverage-coverage03.html" title="Coverage/coverage03">Coverage03</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Coverage03 example</td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
               <td style="column-width:30%">
                  <a href="Patient-patient01.html" title="Patient/patient01">Patient01</a>
               </td>
               <td>DEQM Patient01 example</td>
            </tr>
         </tbody>
      </table>
   </p>
</div>
